Finding Aid for Provost and Executive Vice-President for Academic Affairs (University of Michigan) Staff Files
Bentley Historical Library
- Swain, Mary Ann, 1970-1993; 75 linear feet
  - Topical Files, 1984-1993
    - 1982-1993, 3 linear feet
      - Academic Services Board (ASB), 1989-1991 (Box 386)
      - Affirmative Action, 1989-1992 (Box 386)
      - Architecture and Urban Planning, School of, 1990-1991 (Box 386)
      - Art, School of, 1990-1991 (Box 386)
      - Association of Multicultural Scientists, 1991 (Box 386)
      - Business Administration, School of, 1991-1992 (Box 386)
      - Career ladder for lecturers,1985 (Box 386)
      - Classroom Scheduling Review Committee, 1992-1993 (Box 386)
      - Communicative Disorders Clinic (CDC)
        - General, 1980-1993; 2 folders (Box 386)
        - Shady Trails Camp, 1986-1992; 2 folders (Box 386)
      - Comprehensive Studies Program (CSP), 1989-1993; 2 folders (Box 386)
      - Deans retreat on diversity, 1987-1990 (Box 386)
      - Douglas R. Woolley, Interim Registrar, 1992-1993 (Box 386)
      - Education, School of
        - Combined Program in Education and Psychology, 1982-1993; 3 folders (Box 386)
        - General, 1986-1991 (Box 386)
        - Extension Activity, 1982-1987 (Box 386)
        - Research Centers, 1983-1985 (Box 386)
      - Engineering, College of, 1992-1993 (Box 386)
      - Enrollment Deposits, 1990-1991 (Box 386)
      - Enrollment Working Group (EWG), 1992 (Box 387)
      - Equity Within the Classroom: Graduating Minority Students, 1992 (Box 387)
      - Ethics, 1989 (Box 387)
      - Extension, General, 1991-1992 (Box 387)
      - Faculty Grievances, 1990-1992 (Box 411)
      - Faculty Retention, 1989 (Box 387)
      - Faculty Retirement, 1991-1992 (Box 387)
      - Graduate Student Appointments by Race, 1992 (Box 387)
      - Graduate Studies, Rackham School of, 1990
        - Students of Color of Rackham, 1992 (Box 387)
      - Graduation Rate/Parental Income, 1991 (Box 387)
      - K-12 Michigan Partnership (Michigan Partnership for New Education), 1990 (Box 387)
      - K-12 Research (Box 387)
      - Kinesiology (Box 387)
      - Literature, Science and the Arts (LS&A), College of
        - General, 1989-1992; 2 folders (Box 387)
        - Biological Sciences, 1984-1987 (Box 387)
        - Central Committee on the Undergraduate Experiences (CCUE), 1990-1992; 3 folders
          - Subcommittees
            - Counseling, 1991 (Box 387)
            - Graduation and Distribution Requirements, 1991 (Box 387)
            - Pedagogy, 1990-1991 (Box 387)
            - Pre-concentration years, 1990-1991 (Box 387)
        - Chemistry, 1984-1993 (Box 387)
        - Departments, 1988-1993 (Box 387)
        - English Composition Project (Bill Ingram), 1990-1992 (Box 387)
        - Extension Activity, 1982 (Box 387)
        - Physics Department, Long-range planning, 1984-1990 (Box 387)
        - Response to Salary Equity Study, 1989 (Box 411)
        - Sociology of Love, 1991 (Box 387)
      - Medical School: Green, Robert A., 1989-1992 (Box 387)
      - Medical School: Review of Clinical Track Appointments, 1986-1990 (Box 387)
      - Mission Statement, University of Michigan, 1989-1991 (Box 387)
      - Minority Fellowships and Scholarships, 1991 (Box 388)
      - Music, School of, 1988-1992 (Box 388)
      - National Science Foundation (NSF): Natural science requirements, and women and minorities, 1990-1994 (Box 388)
      - Natural Resources and Environment, School of, 1983-1994; 3 folders (Box 388)
      - Nursing, School of, 1990-1993 (Box 388)
      - Nursing, School of: Extension, 1982-1988 (Box 388)
      - Pharmacy, College of, 1987-1992 (Box 388)
      - Provost's Commission on Recruitment, Success and Graduation of Students of Color, 1991-1993 (Box 388)
      - Registrar's Office, 1992-1993 (Box 388)
      - Social Work, School of, 1982-1993 (Box 388)
      - Social Work, School of: Extension, 1982-1986 (Box 388)
      - Steering Committee on University Events (SCUE), 1987-1991 (Box 388)
      - Student Accounting System Replacement Project Steering Committee, 1993 (Box 388)
      - Student Data Access Project
        - Data Availability Plan Committee, 1990-1993 (Box 388)
        - Official Third Week Count (O3WC), 1990-1993 (Box 388)
        - University of Michigan/Detroit Public Schools, 1989-1991; 2 folders (Box 388)
        - University Financial Aid Advisory Committee (UFAAC), 1986-1990 (Box 388)
        - University Information System (UIS) Overview, 1992 (Box 388)
        - University Since BAM: Twenty Years of Progress, 1990 (Box 388)
  - Schools and Colleges, 1979-1992
    - Budget Files, 1981-1992
      - 1981/82-1987/88
        - Architecture and Urban Planning, College of, 4 folders (Box 127)
        - Art, School of, 3 folders (Box 127)
        - Business Administration, School of, 3 folders (Box 127)
        - Dentistry, School of, 5 folders (Box 127)
        - Education, School of, 4 folders (Box 127)
        - Engineering, College of, 6 folders (Box 127)
        - Graduate Studies, Rackham School of, 3 folders (Box 128)
        - Information and Library Science, School of, 5 folders (Box 128)
        - Law School, 4 folders (Box 128)
        - Literature, Science and the Arts, College of, 5 folders (Box 128)
        - Medical School, 4 folders (Box 128)
        - Music, School of, 5 folders (Box 128)
        - Natural Resources, School of, 3 folders (Box 129)
        - Nursing, School of, 5 folders (Box 129)
        - Pharmacy, College of, 1979/80-1987/88; 5 folders (Box 129)
        - Public Health, School of, 5 folders (Box 129)
        - Social Work, School of, 5 folders (Box 129)
      - 1990/91
        - General, 1988-1991; 2 folders (Box 195)
        - Architecture and Urban Planning, College of (Box 195)
        - Art, School of (Box 195)
        - Business Administration, School of (Box 195)
        - Dentistry, School of (Box 195)
        - Education, School of (Box 195)
        - Engineering, College of (Box 195)
        - Graduate Studies, Rackham School of (Box 195)
        - Law, School of (Box 195)
        - Literature, Science, and the Arts, College of (Box 195)
        - Medical School (Box 195)
        - Music, School of (Box 195)
        - Natural Resources, School of (Box 195)
        - Nursing, School of (Box 195)
        - Pharmacy, College of (Box 195)
        - Public Health, School of (Box 195)
        - School of Information and Library Science (Box 195)
        - Social Work, School of (Box 195)
      - 1987/89
        - General Budget Information (Box 289)
      - 1988-1989
        - Communicative Disorders Clinic (Box 289)
        - Museum of Art (Box 289)
      - 1989-1990
        - General Budget Information (Box 289)
        - Budget Requests from Robert Holmes's Units (Box 289)
        - Academic Planning and Analysis, Office of (Box 289)
        - Affirmative Action, Office of (Box 289)
        - Centers
          - Education of Women (CEW) (Box 289)
          - Educational Improvement through Collaboration (CEIC) (Box 289)
            (includes Faculty Against Institutional Racism-FAIR))
          - Human Growth and Development (CHGD) (Box 289)
          - Research on Learning and Teaching (CRLT) (Box 289)
        - Communicative Disorders Clinic (CDC) (Box 289)
        - Developmental and Reproductive Biology (DRB) (Box 289)
        - Extension Service (Box 289)
        - Information Technology Division (ITD) (Box 289)
        - Institutes
          - Gerontology (IOG) (Box 289)
          - Labor and Industrial Relations (ILIR) (Box 289)
          - Public Policy Studies (IPPS) (Box 289)
          - Social Research (ISR) (Box 289)
        - Libraries
          - Bentley Historical Library (Box 289)
          - Clements Library (Box 289)
        - Minority Affairs, Office of (Box 289)
        - Museum of Art (Box 289)
        - Pharmacy, College of (Box 289)
        - Physical Education Division (Box 289)
        - President, Office of (Box 290)
        - Recreational Sports (Box 290)
        - SACUA (Senate Advisory Committee on University Affairs) (Box 290)
        - Vice Presidents
          - Academic Affairs (Box 290)
          - Business and Finance (Box 290)
          - Government Relations (Box 290)
          - Research (Box 290)
          - Student Services (Box 290)
          - University Events (Box 290)
      - 1989-1990
        - General Budget Information (Box 290)
        - Budget Requests from Robert Holmes's Units (Box 290)
        - Academic Planning and Analysis, Office of (Box 290)
        - Affirmative Action, Office of (Box 290)
        - Centers
          - Education of Women (CEW) (Box 290)
          - Educational Improvement through Collaboration (CEIC) (Box 290)
          - Human Growth and Development (CHGD) (Box 290)
          - Research on Learning and Teaching (CRLT) (Box 290)
        - Communicative Disorders Clinic (CDC) (Box 290)
        - Developmental and Reproductive Biology (DRB) (Box 290)
        - Extension Service (Box 290)
        - Information Technology Division (ITD) (Box 290)
        - Institutes
          - Gerontology (IOG) (Box 290)
          - Labor and Industrial Relations (ILIR) (Box 290)
          - Public Policy Studies (IPPS) (Box 290)
          - Social Research (ISR) (Box 290)
        - Libraries
          - Bentley Historical Library (Box 290)
          - Clements Library (Box 290)
        - Minority Affairs, Office of (Box 290)
        - Museum of Art (Box 290)
        - Pharmacy, College of (Box 290)
        - Physical Education Division (Box 290)
        - President, Office of (Box 290)
        - Recreational Sports (Box 290)
        - SACUA (Senate Advisory Committee on University Affairs) (Box 290)
        - Vice Presidents
          - Academic Affairs (Box 290)
          - Business and Finance (Box 290)
          - Government Relations (Box 290)
          - Research (Box 290)
          - Student Services (Box 290)
          - University Events (Box 290)
      - 1991-1992
        - General Budget Information (Box 290)
        - Centers
          - Education of Women (CEW) (Box 290)
          - Research on Learning and Teaching (CRLT) (Box 290)
        - Communicative Disorders Clinic (CDC) (Box 290)
        - Dentistry, School of (Box 290)
        - Extension Service (Box 290)
        - Financial Aid, Office of (Box 290)
        - Information and Library Studies, School of (Box 290)
        - Literature, Science and the Arts, College of (Box 290)
        - Minority Affairs, Office of (Box 290)
        - Music, School of (Box 290)
        - Orientation Office (Box 290)
        - Pharmacy, College of (Box 290)
        - Public Health, School of (Box 290)
        - Social Work, School of (Box 290)
        - Vice President for Student Services (Box 290)
    - Nonbudget Files, 1979-1989
      - 1983-1988
        - Architecture and Urban Planning, College of
          - General (Box 125)
          - Grievance (faculty/staff), 1986-1987; 1 folder (Box 281)
        - Art, School of
          - General (Box 125)
          - Dean Search, 1984 (Box 125)
          - Review (Box 125)
        - Business Administration, School of
          - General (Box 125)
        - Dentistry
          - Progress Reports (Box 125)
          - Transition (Box 125)
        - Education, School of
          - General, 3 folders (Box 125)
          - Grievance, 1987 (Box 281)
          - Program in Psychology and Education (Box 125)
          - Review Process, Schedule of (Box 125)
        - Engineering, College of
          - Extension Activity, 1982 (Box 125)
        - Graduate Studies, Rackham School of (Box 125)
        - Information and Library Science, School of
          - General, 2 folders (Box 125)
          - Extension Activity, 1982 (Box 125)
        - Law School
          - Extension Activity, 1982 (Box 125)
        - Literature, Science and the Arts, College of
          - General, 4 folders (Box 126)
          - Undergraduate Curriculum (Box 126)
        - Medical School
          - General, 2 folders (Box 126)
          - Family Practice, Department of (Box 126)
        - Music, School of
          - General (Box 126)
          - Theater (Box 126)
        - Natural Resources, School of, 2 folders (Box 126)
        - Nursing, School of
          - General, 3 folders (Box 126)
          - Baccalaureate Program, 1982-1984 (Box 126)
        - Public Health, School of
          - General, 2 folders (Box 126)
          - Clinical Research (Box 126)
          - Deanship (Box 126)
      - 1985-1989
        - Public Health, School of (Box 246)
          - General, 1986-1988 (Box 246)
          - Population Planning and International Health Department, 1985-1986 (Box 246)
        - Social Work, School of
          - General, 1988-1989 (Box 246)
          - Appointments and Complaints (faculty/staff), 1988-1989 (Box 284)
      - 1979-1989
        - Architecture and Urban Design, College of
          - General, 1985; 1987-1988 (Box 290)
          - Appointments, Recruitment and Promotions, 1988 (Box 294)
        - Art, School of
          - General, 1987-1988 (Box 290)
          - Appointments, Recruitment and Promotions, 1988 (Box 294)
          - General Counsel Communications (intellectual property dispute), 1988 (Box 294)
        - Center for the Education of Women (review), 1982 (Box 290)
          (briefing book only)
        - Clements Library (review), 1982 (Box 290)
        - Dentistry, School of
          - General
            - 1980, 1984-1986 (Box 291)
            - 1987 (Box 291)
            - 1988-1989 (Box 291)
          - Appointments, Recruitment and Promotions, 1985-1989 (Box 294)
          - Complaints and Grievances (faculty/staff), 1987-1989 (Box 294)
          - Dean Search, 1988-1989 (Box 294)
          - Faculty Evaluations, 1987-1989 (Box 294)
          - Pew National Dental Education Program, 1985-1987 (Box 291)
          - Student Recruitment, 1989 (Box 294)
            [Student records restricted until July 1, 2074 ]
        - Education, School of
          - General, 1986-1988 (Box 291)
          - Speech and Language Pathology Program
            (includes Communicative Disorders Clinic and Camp Shady Trails)
            - General, 1985-1988 (Box 291)
            - Letters of Support, 1987-1988 (Box 291)
        - Engineering, College of, 1987-1988 (Box 291)
        - Extension Service (review, includes budget), 1986 (Box 291)
        - Graduate Studies, Rackham School of
          - General, 1987-1988 (Box 291)
          - Rackham/Research Merger, 1984 (Box 291)
        - Information and Library Studies, School of
          - General, 1987-1988 (Box 291)
          - Appointments, Recruitment and Promotions, 1987-1988 (Box 294)
        - Institute for the Study of Mental Retardation and Related Disabilities (ISMRRD) (review), 1982; 2 folders (Box 291)
        - Literature, Science and the Arts, College of
          - General, 1987-1988 (Box 291)
          - Appointments and Grievances, 1988-1989 (Box 294)
        - Medical School
          - General, 1988 (Box 291)
          - Appointments, Recruitment and Promotions, 1987-1990 (Box 294)
        - Michigan Media
          - General
            - 1978-1979 (Box 291)
            - 1980-1981 (Box 291)
            - 1982-1984 (Box 291)
            - 1985-1986 (Box 291)
            - 1987 (Box 292)
            - 1988-1989 (Box 292)
          - Appointments and Grievances (faculty/staff), 1979; 1983 (Box 294)
          - Budgets, 1987-1988 (Box 292)
          - Reviews
            - 1982-1984 (Box 292)
            - 1986-1987, 2 folders (Box 292)
        - Music, School of
          - General, 1987-1988 (Box 292)
          - Appointments, Recruitment and Promotions, 1987-1988 (Box 294)
          - Extension Courses, 1981-1986 (Box 292)
        - Natural Resources, School of
          - General, 1987-1988 (Box 292)
          - Appointments, Recruitment and Promotions, 1987-1988 (Box 294)
        - Nursing, School of
          - General, 1987-1988 (Box 292)
          - Appointments and Grievances (faculty/staff), 1987-1988 (Box 294)
        - Pharmacy, College of, 1987-1988 (Box 292)
  - Units, 1978-1991
    - Budget Files, 1981-1991
      - 1981/82-1986/87
        - Art, Museum of, 7 folders (Box 136)
        - Bentley Historical Library, 6 folders (Box 136)
        - Center for Continuing Education for Women (CEW), 8 folders (Box 136)
        - Center for Human Growth and Development (CHGD), 7 folders (Box 136)
        - Center for Research on Learning and Teaching (CRLT), 8 folders (Box 136)
        - Clements Library, 8 folders (Box 137)
        - Communicative Disorders Clinic, 3 folders (Box 137)
        - Developmental and Reproductive Biology, 6 folders (Box 137)
        - Extension Service, 6 folders (Box 137)
        - Gerontology, Institute of, 6 folders (Box 137)
        - Institute for Labor and Industrial Relations (ILIR), 8 folders (Box 137)
        - Institute of Public Policy Studies (IPPS), 10 folders (Box 138)
        - Michigan Media, 7 folders (Box 138)
        - Physical Education, Division of, 8 folders (Box 138)
        - University Library, 2 folders (Box 138)
      - 1987/88
        - Center for Continuing Education of Women (CEW) (Box 246)
        - Center for Human Growth and Development (CHGD) (Box 246)
      - 1988/89
        - Budget Conferences Notes (Box 246)
        - Center for Continuing Education of Women (CEW) (Box 246)
        - Center for Human Growth and Development (CHGD) (Box 246)
        - Center for Research on Learning and Teaching (CRLT) (Box 246)
        - Clements Library (Box 246)
        - Developmental and Reproductive Biology (Box 246)
        - Institute of Gerontology (IOG) (Box 246)
        - Institute of Labor and Industrial Relations (ILIR) (Box 246)
        - Institute for Public Policy Studies (IPPS) (Box 246)
      - 1990/91
        - General (Box 197)
        - Art, Museum of (Box 197)
        - Bentley Historical Library (Box 197)
        - Communicative Disorders Clinics (CDC) (Box 197)
        - Center for the Education of Women (CEW) (Box 197)
        - Center for Human Growth and Development (CHGD) (Box 197)
        - Clements Library (Box 197)
        - Center for Research on Learning and Teaching (CRLT) (Box 197)
        - Extension Service (Box 197)
        - Holmes, Robert B., Units reporting to (Box 197)
        - Information Technology Division (ITD) (Box 197)
        - Institute for Social Research (ISR) (Box 197)
        - Institute for Labor and Industrial Relations (ILIR) (Box 197)
        - Institute of Public Policy Studies (IPPS) (Box 197)
        - Library, University (Box 197)
        - Physical Education, Division of (Box 197)
        - Recreational Sports (Box 197)
        - Reproductive Sciences Program (Box 197)
        - Senate Advisory Committee on University Affairs (SACUA) (Box 197)
        - Student Information Services, Office of (Box 197)
        - University Relations (Box 197)
    - Non-Budget Files, 1978-1990
      - 1978-1988
        (includes some earlier materials)
        - Art, Museum of
          - Background Materials, 1973-1978 (Box 130)
          - Correspondence, 1979-1980; 1982-1984; 2 folders (Box 130)
          - Directorship
            - Acting, 1980 (Box 130)
            - Review, 1978 (Box 281)
            - Search, 1979-1980 (Box 282)
          - Maurer, Evan, 1981-1988 (Box 130)
          - Waller, Bret, Resignation, 1980 (Box 130)
          - Miscellaneous, 1983-1986 (Box 130)
        - Center for Continuing Education of Women (CEW)
          - General, 1983-1989; 2 folders (Box 130)
          - Awards, Scholarships and Grants, 1979 (Box 130)
          - Director Searches
            - 1984-1985 (Box 282)
            - 1987-1988 (Box 282)
          - Evening Program, 1984-1986 (Box 130)
          - Executive Committee, 1976-1983 (Box 130)
          - Nontraditional Students, 1976-1980 (Box 130)
          - Review, 1982; 2 folders (Box 130)
          - Women in Science, 1979-1985; 2 folders (Box 130)
          - Miscellaneous, 1979-1985; 2 folders (Box 131)
        - Center for Human Growth and Development (CHGD)
          - General
            - 1981 (Box 131)
            - 1986 (Box 131)
          - Amphibian Center, 1979-1982 (Box 131)
          - Child Development Research Facility, 1978-1986 (Box 131)
          - Council of Programs in Human Development, 1981-1983 (Box 131)
          - Craniofacial Growth, 1983 (Box 282)
          - Director Searches
            - 1979-1980, 1 folder
              - 1983 (Box 131)
          - Health Psychology, 1984 (Box 131)
          - Long Range Planning, 1986 (Box 131)
          - Personnel, 1979-1980 (Box 131)
          - Problems/Resolutions, 1982-1983; 1 folder (Box 282)
          - Reproductive Endocrinology, 1981 (Box 131)
          - Review Committee
            - 1972 (Box 131)
            - 1978 (Box 131)
          - Rules of Governance, 1979-1982 (Box 131)
          - Space/Planning/Courses/Equipment, 1978-1983 (Box 131)
          - Miscellaneous, 1978-1986 (Box 131)
        - Center for Research on Learning and Teaching (CRLT)
          - Director, Interim, 1983 (Box 132)
          - Fricke, Benno, 1981 (Box 132)
          - Instructional Computing, 1985 (Box 132)
          - Reviews
            - 1980 (Box 132)
            - 1982-1983 (Box 132)
          - Miscellaneous, 1979-1984 (Box 132)
        - Clements Library
          - Review, 1981-1982 (Box 132)
          - Miscellaneous, 1978-1986 (Box 132)
        - Counseling
          - Review, 1984 (Box 132)
        - Developmental Reproductive Biology, 1984 (Box 132)
        - Extension Service
          - Adult Education Program, 1982-1983 (Box 132)
          - Advisory Committee, 1981-1983 (Box 132)
          - Continuing Education Unit Review Committee, 1984 (Box 132)
          - Governor's Commission on Extension, 1984 (Box 132)
          - Joint Program UM Flint and Dearborn, 1976-1982 (Box 132)
          - Overload, 1977-1980 (Box 132)
          - Program, 1984 (Box 132)
          - University Conference Activities, 1986 (Box 132)
          - Miscellaneous, 1976-1985; 2 folders (Box 133)
        - Gerontology, Institute of (IOG)
          - Biology of Aging, 1979-1980 (Box 133)
          - Bylaws, 1983-1985 (Box 133)
          - Director Search, 1981 (Box 282)
        - Institute of Labor and Industrial Relations (ILIR)
          - General, 1975-1983; 2 folders (Box 133)
          - Annual Reports, 1976/77; 1979/80 (Box 133)
          - Conservation, Employee Participation In, Japan, 1983 (Box 133)
          - Director Search, 1982-1983 (Box 133)
          - Executive Committee, 1983-1985 (Box 133)
          - Micro Information Storage and Retrieval, 1976-1983 (Box 133)
          - Reviews
            - 1980-1981, 3 folders
              - Folder 1 (Box 133)
              - Folders 2-3 (Box 134)
            - 1981-82, 3 folders (Box 134)
          - Wayne State University, Separation of Programs, 1981/82 (Box 134)
          - Miscellaneous, 1975-1984 (Box 134)
        - Institute of Public Policy Studies (IPPS)
          - General, 1976-1977 (Box 134)
          - Director Searches
            - 1978-1979, 1 folder (Box 282)
            - 1981 (Box 282)
            - 1982-1983 (Box 134)
          - International Program Proposal, 1977-1980 (Box 134)
          - Review, 1979 (Box 134)
          - Miscellaneous, 1980-1984 (Box 134)
        - Institute of Science and Technology (IST), 1986 (Box 134)
        - Institute for Social Research (ISR), 1986 (Box 134)
        - Institute for the Study of Mental Retardation and Related Disabilities
          - Director Search, 1980 (Box 283)
        - Mental Health Research Institute (MHRI), 1984 (Box 135)
        - Physical Education, Division of, 1981-1984 (Box 135)